<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="faq">Frequently Asked Questions\n</string>
    <string name="call_now">Call now</string>
    <string name="leave_email">Leave an email</string>
    <string name="find_locations">Find Locations</string>
    <string name="no_questions_found">No Questions Found</string>
    <string name="help_line_number" translatable="false">8000000000</string>
    <string name="contact_email" translatable="false">support@mifos.org</string>
    <string name="user_query">User Query</string>
    <string name="no_app_to_support_action">There is no application that support this action</string>

    <string-array name="faq_qs">
        <item>How do I apply for new loan account?</item>
        <item>Where can I view my profile information?</item>
        <item>Where can I see my Savings Accounts Transactions?</item>
        <item>What is the use of QR Code?</item>
        <item>How to create a beneficiary using QR Code?</item>
        <item>How to make a payment for a Loan Account?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faq_ans">
        <item>To apply for loan account, click on \"Apply for Loan\" given on the Home Screen.
        </item>
        <item>You can view your profile information by clicking on the User Image present on Home
            Screen.
        </item>
        <item>To view your savings account transactions, navigate to the Accounts Sections, click on
            the required savings account, click on three dots present on top right and select
            Transactions option.
        </item>
        <item>QrCode for any loan or savings accounts can be shared with other users which will
            allow them to create a beneficiary.
        </item>
        <item>In order to create a Beneficiary, goto Beneficiary option from Home Screen then click
            on the circular button present on bottom right, choose the option to Scan which opens
            your device camera, scan the QR Code of other person for which you want to create a
            beneficiary, after filling in the other required detail you will be able to create a
            Beneficiary using QR Code.
        </item>
        <item>To make a payment for a loan account, navigate to the Accounts Sections, choose LOAN
            then open your required Loan Account and click on Make Payment option.
        </item>

    </string-array>

</resources>